

Gianluigi Mucciolo

Al & DevOps Engineer on AWS

g.mucciolo91(at)gmail.com

in mucciolo91

ggiallo28

ggiallo28

EDUCATION

MSc in Information Engineering University of Salerno - Technische Universität Wien, GPA: 4.0

BSc in Information Engineering University of Salerno, GPA: 3.3 2010 - 2015

LANGUAGES

Italian (Native)

English (Fluent, Certified B2)

INTERESTS

Artificial Intelligence

Technical Meetings

Learning & Self Improvement

CAREER PROFILE

Gianluigi Mucciolo has a master's degree in Computer Science and operates on Amazon Web Services. He has many years of experience in the use of Agile and DevOps Methodologies, works in the field of Artificial Intelligence and Big Data, and carries out training activities by providing official AWS courses. He can successfully work in a team environment as well as independently, work under pressure and multi-task, deliver quality results.

EXPERIENCES

AWS Technical Trainer Champion

Amazon, Italy 2018 - Present

He provides courses in AWS Business Essentials, AWS Technical Essentials, Architecting on AWS, Systems Operations on AWS, Developing on AWS, Big Data on AWS, Machine Learning on AWS, Data Warehousing in AWS, Deep Learning on AWS, Security on AWS and Planning and Designing Databases on AWS.

AI & DevOps Engineer on AWS

Claranet, Italy 2017 - Present

He carries out the migration, the definition of new infrastructures, monitoring and maintenance activities. He also use Amazon Web Services for Machine Learning and Big Data.

Quality Assurance & Testing

NTT DATA, Italy 2017 - 2017

Huawei consultant on OCS project for Telecom Italia.

CERTIFICATIONS

AWS Certified Database - Specialty - get 2019 - mar 2023

AWS Certified Security - Specialty - dic 2019 - dic 2022

AWS Certified Machine Learning - Specialty- set 2019 - set 2022

AWS Certified Developer - Associate - ott 2018 - ott 2021

AWS Certified Big Data - Specialty - set 2018 - set 2021

AWS Certified SysOps Administrator - Associate- set 2018 - set 2021

AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate - feb 2018 - feb 2021

SKILLS & PROFICIENCY

CloudFormation, Terraform, Ansible	
AWS CI/CD Tools & Jenkins	
Python, SageMaker & MXNet	
ETL, Kinesis, Redshift & Athena	
AWS System Manager & CLI	
Serverless & Microservices,	